- ♪ In the
not too distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪˯ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked
at Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him
into space ♪
[ rocket rumbling ]
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He’ll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we’ll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
Robot roll call!
- Cambot!
- Pan left!
- Gypsy!
- Hi, girl!
- Tom Servo!
- What a cool guy.
- Croooow!
- Wisecracker!
♪ If you’re wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should
really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery
Science Theater 3000 ♪
[ both laughing ]
- Oh, what are you guys doing?
You're supposed to be helping me
crunch numbers
for that navigational
plot thing.
- I’m not going back, Jim.
- Oh, come on, not this again.
You guys, I’ve been waiting.
- I’m in love, Jim.
- Oh, you!
- Hi, everybody. Welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
I’m Joel Robinson.
If you haven't
already noticed,
my bots,
Tom Servo and Crow,
seem to be obsessing
on the Elias Sandoval episode
of Star Trek.
- I like it here
on Omicron Seti III, Jim.
- It really is wonderful here,
Captain Kirk.
- Five seconds
to commercial time.
Can I be of any help, Joel?
- No, I just have
to get them mad,
and then they seem
to snap out of it.
You’re incapable
of feeling love, Spock.
- I would not say such things
if I were you, Jim.
- You belong
in the circus, Spock,
right next
to the dog-faced boy.
- That’s enough, Captain.
- We’ll be right back.
[ both laughing ]
- [ imitating William Shatner ]
But does she know
what she’s getting, Spock?
Your mother was a computer, and
your father was an encyclopedia.
- My mother was a teacher
and my father an ambassador.
- Knock it off, you two.
Aunt Dan
and Lemon are calling.
- [ hissing ]
- [ on TV ] Now, remember,
Hobie, you stay away
from the kids
down by the liquor store.
[ changes channel ]
- Hey!
- Baywatch can wait
for now, Frank.
With the money we earn
from this week's invention,
we won’t have
to watch Baywatch.
We’ll be able to live it.
- So that means I could be
just like David Hasselhoff.
I better practice sucking
in my gut.
- You’re one to talk,
eh, Frank?
- [ laughing ]
Hey!
- Well, bubby,
our invention this week
is based on
those new high-priced TVs
that allow you to check out
several other channels
on the small screens
while you watch
one program
on the big screen.
Our invention goes
that one better.
You see, it actually allows you
to check out and see
what you would be doing
in your life at that moment
if you weren’t
at home watching TV.
It’s called the U-View.
Check it out, Frank.
[ changes channel ]
- Hey, it's a beautiful,
bright, sunny day out,
and what’s this?
Michelle Pfeiffer, Debra Winger
and Holly Hunter
are motioning
for me to come over
and join them
in a game of touch football?
Wow!
They needed a fourth player,
and I just happened along.
Wow!
Hey, that’s Elvis Costello!
He just happened
to walked by, and he's...
Looks like he's asking us
to come over to his house
to hear some new songs
he’s working on.
Wow!
So that's
what would have happened
if I had gone out today.
Boy!
I'm really glad I...
stayed inside to...
watch Baywatch.
- Oh. I'll try that.
[ changes channel ]
I’m sitting in a Perkins
looking at a menu.
Well, that doesn't
seem to be
like I’m missing
anything...
Whoa! What?
Oh, Henry Kissinger
and Richard Nixon
are shyly approaching my table.
They’re shaking my hand
and patting me on the back.
Henry’s giving me a Kissinger
and Associates sweatshirt.
Nixon, what is he doing?
He’s pointing at the menu.
Ah, he’s recommending
the club sandwich.
[ laughing ]
Oh, I do love this, Frank,
but not as much as I love
sitting at home
watching Baywatch.
[ changes channel ]
- [ on TV ] Oh, no,
I’m in big trouble.
I never should have hung out
with the kids
down by the liquor store.
- Well, sirs,
our invention may look
like just an ordinary
Weber Grill,
but it’s much,
much more than that.
Yes, it’s
the Andrew Lloyd Webber Grill.
[ laughing ]
- Hey, everybody
come and get it.
I've got a whole ream of
Andrew Lloyd Webber scores,
and they’re
all ready to barbecue.
- Yes, now you can take out
your aggression
on the theater world’s most
inescapable troll-like composer.
- Yeah, just stick any
of his many overblown scores
in the Andrew Lloyd Webber
Grill,
and they’ll burn quickly
and efficiently.
- Whether it’s Cats
or Phantom of the Opera.
- Starlight Express
or Evita.
- Hey, wait,
I kind of liked Evita.
- No time for sentiment, Joel.
We’ve got to burn
Aspects of Love and Chess.
- Wait a minute.
Andrew Lloyd Webber
didn’t write Chess.
It was Tim Rice
and those guys from ABBA.
- Oh, I think the Andrew Lloyd
Webber Grill can handle them,
and we might as well
burn the score
- to Annie while we’re at it.
- Mmm!
- Hey, what
do you think, sirs?
[ Crow and Tom coughing ]
- Oh, man, Elvis is holding up
a picture of Andrew Lloyd Webber
and making fun of it.
Holly, Debra, Michelle, and I
are having a good laugh
at his expense.
We’re having a great time.
Why did I stay inside today?
Why, why, why?
Oh, wow,
McKenna’s Gold is on.
- Well, Joel,
your experiment this week
will make you wish you were
singing duets
with Patty LuPone
at Mandy Patinkin’s house.
It's an experiment in padding
from Roger Corman,
and it's called
Swamp Diamonds,
but first a short film
called What To Do On A Date.
You should be able to relate
to that, right, Frank?
- Shh!
- All right,
who wants an overture?
- [ alarm sounding ]
- I do! I do!
- Let's beat it! Ohh!
[ coughing ]
- I need to know
what not to do on a date.
- What, does she have a Ph.D.
in dating?
- Oh, no, this is like having
your mom tell you about sex.
- These two are on a date?
- No, no.
- This is a story about
what to do on a date.
- Goofus and Gallant?
- It begins one early
summer afternoon.
It begins with Jeff.
- Ha! Good one, Jeff.
- And Kay.
- And a human ear.
- And Nick.
- Oh, I meant to do that.
- Bye, Nick.
What a loser.
- Of course, you
may not have a problem
about what to do on a date,
but Nick, well,
he has a real dating problem.
If he took Kay out on a date,
what would they do?
Where would they go?
- [ imitates glass breaking ]
Dennis!
- No, you can’t inject puberty.
It has to happen over time.
- Jeff, I’ll get
my tennis racket.
- Okay, Nick, but hurry.
- And, Jeff,
would you quit stalking me?
- Bet he wishes he had a life.
Man, what a loser.
♪ Dubba dubba deeba
dubba dubba ♪
Hmm? Oh.
- My God, Kay’s been missing
since last February!
- Hey, what about asking Kay
to come to the community center
with us on Friday to fix up
that scavenger sale?
We could make it
a double date.
- You looked in my book,
didn’t you?
- What?
- You heard what I said.
[ all humming Psycho theme ]
- That's no way
to take a girl on a date,
helping to fix up
the scavenger sale?
Is it?
- Why not?
- On a first date?
- First date?
- Yeah.
Well, Kay’s a swell girl.
- [ groans ]
- I was thinking
of calling her,
maybe ask her
to the show Friday.
Good picture, Wagon Train.
- [ snickers ]
- Well, hurry up and call her
and let’s get going.
I still have
to get my things yet.
- Call her now?
- Sure. You know
the number, don't you?
- Okay.
- But I’ve got
a Forever Plaid audition.
- I’m kidding, I’m kidding.
Hang up the phone.
- With each dial,
he comes closer and closer
to the most humiliating moment
of his life.
- What if she says no?
- She will.
- Hello?
- Oh, hello, Kay?
- No.
- This is Nick Baxter.
- Oh, hello, Nick,
how are you?
- I hurt inside.
- Fine, thanks.
Say, Kay, next Friday,
would you like to see
Wagon Train at the movies?
- I didn’t think so, bye.
- Oh, I’m sorry Nick.
I suppose you’ve got
your mind made up to see it?
- You’ve seen it?
She’s already seen it.
- Hang up.
- Well, ask her
about the scavenger sale.
Go ahead.
- Uh, Kay, you wouldn't
want to help
get the scavenger sale ready
at the community center,
would you?
- How many ways can I say no?
- Oh, I’ve been hearing
about that.
Yes, I’d like to very much.
- Is it okay if I bring
my boyfriend, Dave?
- You would?
All right.
I’ll call for you then
about 7:00?
Bye.
- I better change my pants.
- I sure didn’t think she’d go
to a place like that for a date.
- With a loser like me.
- Where’s my racket?
- I should spank myself.
- Oh, ready?
- You know, you better think
some more, fellow,
about what to do on a date.
- She said yes, okay?
- You think she’ll
have a good time?
What do you
suppose I’ll have to do?
- Oh, yeah, who wouldn’t
have a good time?
[ jaunty music ]
- ♪ June is bustin' out
all over ♪
- Aaron Copeland
throws a party.
- Now, you may not have thought
of this sort of thing
as a place to take a date,
but it looks like it
could be fun.
- Doesn't it?! Doesn’t it?!
- Boy, this is fun,
with the used lamps
and the festoonery. Whoa.
- This party is getting
out of control.
- A group doing things together.
- Herds.
- Pretty good idea
for a first date.
Plenty to do, plenty of people
to talk to.
- Plenty of opportunities
to screw up big time.
- But let’s see if Nick and Kay
are enjoying it.
- No amount of dust could make
this thing look any older.
- Boy, that is an old-timer.
- And the dust comment
proves to be a major
miscalculation on Kay’s part.
- "Boy, that is an old-timer."
What was I thinking?
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
- Kay’s worked
on the kill floor.
She knows
where to deliver the blow.
- Can you help me
put this sign up?
- Oh, sure.
- Sure, I’ll do everything.
This relationship
is suffocating me.
- I couldn't quite reach
that far.
- How’s this?
- Looks a bit gangly, oaf.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Ooh! Ow! Son of a--Mmm!
Ooh ooh!
- Say, Kay.
- Will you marry me?
- Are you really having
a good time?
- Of course, I am.
I’m glad you thought
of coming here.
- So am I.
- I remember
when I was that age.
- Yes, this was a good idea.
- Oh, Kay, how about helping
with refreshments for the day?
- All right.
- For the Crips or the Bloods?
- See you later.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
- Sorry it didn’t work out.
- Got any more tacks?
- I think they’re over there
by the door.
- I got to cut him loose.
- Yes, it was a good idea
to come here.
- At first.
- How does Jeff get ideas
like that?
- From the voices inside
his head.
- Hey, what’s this?
Maybe this is where Jeff
gets ideas.
- The lunch menu?
- A list
of coming activities.
A bike trip--
that could be a lot of fun.
A chance to do things
with a group to get acquainted.
- Now, is this fantasy?
- It does look like a good time
if your partner likes it.
- That’s a big "if."
One bad idea could mean the end
of your relationship.
- Would Kay enjoy a bike trip?
Or a weenie roast?
- Nick, no!
- Another group date,
a chance to learn
the give and take of working
and playing together.
Not much arranging needed,
not much expense,
and that can be important.
Could be a fine date
if Kay would like it.
- Kay, Kay, Kay!
What about my needs?
- ...go to a baseball game,
a date
that’s not too involved,
one you can carry
through comfortably.
- Oops, Nick strikes out.
- And there are all sorts
of other sports events,
inexpensive dates
most of them.
Swimming meets, for example.
- Are very dull.
- You can find many good ideas
for dates.
- Hey, hey,
our luggage is here! Whoo!
- Dates that give you a good
chance to get acquainted...
- and dates that you don't...
- Heh heh heh, yeah!
- ...have to worry
too much about in advance.
- Nick, snap out of it!
- It was a good deal
coming here tonight,
double dating
with Jeff and Phyllis.
- But mostly Jeff.
- When all four are good friends
and enjoy the same things,
double dates
can be lots of fun.
Or you can ask Kay to go on
dates with you alone
if you plan for what she enjoys.
- [ humming adult film music ]
- Hey, you loafer.
What are you doing over there?
- Oh, thought you were talking
to me, sorry.
Awkward.
- Fine thing.
As soon as Kay isn't
around to supervise,
you go off on a vacation.
- You know, maestro,
I don’t think your date ideas
are so original.
- Hmm?
- What?
- About what to do
on a date, I mean.
- Ah, sorry.
- What I'd like to know is,
how can you pick out
what a girl would like to do?
A certain girl, I mean.
- Well, you might ask her.
- Oh, I should
have thought of that.
- Yeah, Nick’s looking for you.
- Jeez, hide me.
- Is he good company?
He always seems so quiet.
- We get along all right.
He's got
a good sense of humor,
and he hasn’t run
out of things to say yet.
- He will.
- He’s kind of cute.
You going to date him again?
- I don’t know.
Besides, he hasn’t asked me.
George, get out of there.
- I’m hungry.
- If you want to do something,
take the Cokes out there.
- Okay.
- All set?
- I think so.
- Why can’t Nick be fun
like George is?
- Come and get it, everybody!
- Come on, we eat!
- Eat at your own risk.
- The sensuous pagan ritual
begins.
- Mmm!
- Hi, stranger.
- I decided to come
out of hiding.
- Is she Salman Rushdie?
- You make the sandwiches?
- Nah, just the Cokes.
- Nick, other people
have to eat, too.
[ all talking at once ]
- Oh, Nick, you take me
to the best places.
- Oh, oh, Nick's got back.
- Your table, Madame.
- Thank you, sir.
- Boy, they’re a regular
Tracy and Hepburn up there.
Look at them up there.
- This is fun, isn’t it?
- Yeah, you sure you like to do
things like this?
- Sure.
- What do you want
from me, Nick?
- I thought girls wanted
fellas to take them
to fancy places,
spend lots of money.
- Not this girl.
- You know, I sort of
like things like this, too.
You won’t laugh, I like to go
on bicycle trips, too.
[ all laughing ]
Do you?
- And miniature golf.
Do you like that?
- Yeah, and weenie roasts
and square dances.
- And baseball games
and taffy pulls.
I think they’re swell.
- Say, you like to do
lots of things, don’t you?
- Hey, you read the list, too.
- Say, Kay, next Friday, there's
going to be a weenie roast,
or there will be a bowling party
if you’d rather do that.
- It won’t work, Nick.
- Or we could go
to the band concert.
- Well, I’d enjoy going
to the weenie roast very much.
- With someone else.
- Unless you’d
rather go bowling.
- No, I’d rather go
to the weenie roast.
- Let’s not fight, Nick.
It’s our first date.
- If Jeff goes with Phyllis,
we could double-date with them.
- Hey, Nick, come on!
We’re going to break open
the ice cream!
- Okay, be right there!
- Ice cream?
I love this party!
- So we're on again
on Friday?
- Yes, Nick, it’s a date.
- Hey, guys,
what’s a weenie roast?
- Yes, there are lots of things
to do on dates
if you know how to look
for them,
if you plan them with
the other person in mind,
and if you really try to make
sure each date’s a good time.
If you do these things,
you’ll know
what to do on your date.
- But if you're an AV geek,
don't even kid yourself.
[ laughing ]
- Had this been
an actual date,
you would have been
instructed where to go.
- Huh.
So I guess the sculptors
and the painters
got together
and did this thing.
- Yeah, but
you got to watch out
for those Axis Artists,
you know? Yeah.
[ somber woodwinds playing ]
- The bassoon will be played
by Marie Windsor.
- ♪ Oh, swamp diamond ♪
[ imitating electric guitar ]
- Boy, really
perky music here, huh?
- Whoo!
- Oh, Touch Conners?
I don’t think I...
- The credits are done
by a black velvet artist.
- Neal Claudel.
- Introducing and
saying good-bye to Jil Jarmyn.
[ music crescendos ]
- Is that supposed to be
an example of my headache pains?
- Night Gallery,
the lost episodes.
- [ humming to film music ]
[ imitating diving,
strafing warplane ]
- Oh, I know, these are J.J.’s
Good Times paintings.
- Oh!
- Women in Cell Block H.
- I feel like I should take
Prozac after hearing this music.
- Good ol' Roger Corman.
This is going
to go down hard, guys.
- Mm-hmm.
- To be like the Cor-man,
to live like the Cor-man.
- This is a Pink Panther movie.
- Well, whatever it is,
it’s got pretty lousy animation.
- [ jazz playing ]
- Hmm?
- Apparently they’ve seen
the "How To Date" short.
- Well, there goes
the PTA conga line.
[ humming conga music ]
- That’s not Touch Conners,
that’s Mike Connors!
- I love you so much.
- Think so, huh?
- Why honey, I...
I’d just like to stay with you
forever and ever.
- Maybe your daddy told you
my oil well looks good, huh?
- That’s dirty!
- However can you
say such a thing?
- I was only kidding.
- A holiday is declared
when Touch Mike Mannix Connors
arrives in town!
♪ Da dum da dum ♪ Tch!
- The beginning
of the Krewe of Rex.
- Krewe?
- Yeah, they're the clubs
that conduct the Carnival.
- Wow, really festive colors for
a Mardi Gras, brown and yellow.
- [ imitating Ed Wynn ] Welcome,
everyone, to my tiny kingdom.
Ha ha ha!
- And coming up
the Miss Hathaway marching band.
- Oh, Mr. Drysdale!
[ band playing ]
- Sorry, folks, I don’t know how
this float got into the parade!
- Yes, master,
I’m your love slave.
- Yes, I’m a Q-tip.
Please do not insert me
in your ear canal, thank you.
- Cigars! Cigarettes!
- Hey, how many times can
Washington cross the Delaware?
- Viva the fold out couch!
Viva the fold out couch!
[ imitating explosions ]
- Look out!
Ahh!
- And now our tribute
to yellow.
Yellow!
- You know, it’s so exciting.
It leaves me
perfectly speechless.
- Did I tell you that I’ve got
my eye on some new oil land?
- Oh, really?
Well, where is it, honey?
- In some of the meanest country
in the world.
- Serbia?
- Where’s that?
- Swamp land, bayou country,
jungle.
- I didn’t know there was
such a thing around here.
- Where the hell
did you come from?
- I sure would like to go
and see that jungle with you.
- Oh, I doubt that.
That’s real wild country
for such a pretty young lady.
- Hey, it’s Dinah Shore.
- I guess those
are just the horrors
of being
with a wildcat oilman.
- Yes, and
the Shell Answer Man.
- I'll bet you don’t think
I could take it.
- Maybe.
- But I could.
- Think so?
- Why don’t you let me prove it?
- Please don’t touch,
Touch Conners.
- I could do anything
as long as I was with you.
- Tonight on Mannix,
Touch Conners finds intrigue
and romance in bayou country.
♪ Da dun da dun ♪
- You want to go to the bayou?
- Son of a gun,
gonna have big fun.
- Think your daddy
will let you?
- Oh, he’ll let me do
anything with you.
He thinks that you’re going...
- Whoops.
- He thinks
that you’re just wonderful.
- Well, we might try it
at that.
Come on, let’s go.
- ♪ Da dun da dun ♪
- Why, there’s Dad now.
- Honey, will we go
into the bayou all alone,
just the two of us?
- No, baby,
we’ll have to have a guide.
- Oh, you can find your way
without any old guide.
- I’m not sure
I’d live to tell the tale.
- Rrrr! This is getting steamy.
- What’s the matter?
- I’m sorry, mister, I didn’t
mean to scare your little girl.
- Don’t jump out
and start pawing people.
- Be a sport, will you, pal?
Be a sport.
Give me a little money
for a cup of coffee.
- Yeah, okay, Senator.
- Sure.
Here, buy yourself
a dozen cups, black.
- Is it okay if I just get
a couple of cups of coffee
and maybe some donuts?
I’m just going to stir a bit
of half-and-half in it, okay?
Okay?
- Played Touch Conners
like a piano.
Hey, Mr. Mailer, how’s
The Naked and the Dead going?
- Hey, it’s Pope Ed Asner.
- [ imitating Ted Knight ] Let
me kiss your ring, Lou! Mmm...
- [ imitating Ed Wynn ]
Hello, everybody, hello.
The king commands you to get me
another drink!
- Here's a novel idea--
the parade stays still
and the crowd moves.
It’s a new concept
from ConglomCo.
[ humming ]
- We're crayfish!
Crack us in half and suck
the meat out of our tails!
Ha ha ha ha!
- Oh, the Banana Splits haven’t
aged very well, have they?
- I do not know what we are.
Perhaps we are Gauchos,
olé.
- Gay caballeros.
- Hmm.
- And this must be Children of
Paradise all of a sudden.
Whoa, gee.
- Boy, the joy is just
pouring off those clowns.
- Mm-hmm!
- Man,
this looks like home movies
of my parents' wedding.
- What a great place
for a date.
- Hey, look,
it’s Fred Mertz in Gigi.
[ French accent ]
♪ Lick it up ♪
♪ Lick it
like a piece of cake ♪
Ha ha ha!
What do you think?
- Can you see all right, baby?
- Oh, just perfect, honey.
- Hey, buddy, could you spare
a little old dime?
- I just gave you...
- Hey, what gives?
- Say, just a minute.
You got quite a bit of my money,
didn’t you?
- I don’t know what
you’re talking about, bud.
- Come on, hand it over.
- Let go of me.
- [ woman gasps ]
- All right, Charlie,
let’s go see the judge.
- ♪ I’m a lot like you were ♪
- Oh, great, Joel!
That was really great.
Look, I got to go.
I got some stuff to do.
- Hold on a second, Crow.
We're going to do
an old Simon and Garfunkel tune
called The Boxer,
and you can help me by singing
the la-la-la parts, okay?
♪ I am just a poor boy
and... ♪
- Hi, Joel. Crow.
- Hi.
- Tom Servo, hey, hey, buddy,
old pal, join us.
- Okay. Sure thing.
Oh, say guys,
saw that short on dating.
Thinking
of asking that Gypsy out.
What do you think?
- Oh, Tom, are you sure
you want to do that?
I mean, I'm positive Gypsy likes
you as another fellow robot,
but are you sure she wants
to go out on a date?
- Nonsense!
I think she’d go out with you
in a minute, Tommy Gun.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, you’ve heard
of a mercy date.
- Hey, Crow, come on.
She's probably
just busy running
the higher functions
of the ship.
- Yeah, he’s right.
Besides,
after the intense discomfort
of your almost
sibling-like relationship
sends the date into the crapper,
you'll feel
the hot sting of embarrassment
on your cheeks for months.
- Okay,
I guess you’re right.
Stupid idea.
Just wanted to see what
all the fuss about dating was.
- You know, Tom, it probably
wouldn’t hurt to ask her.
- Really? Yeah, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay!
Any advice?
- Yeah, just be yourself,
you know, don’t get nervous.
- Don’t invoice her for
your expenditures on the date.
- Okay, good.
- I probably wouldn’t show her
my Hummel collection just yet.
- Point taken. Mm-hmm.
- Avoid boring her with your
knowledge of war atrocities.
- Oh, I’m not stupid.
- You know, Tom, you’re going
to need someplace to take her.
- Yeah, not a lot going on up
here, though.
Weenie roast is right out.
[ chuckles ] Hmm...
- Is hardcore on video?
- Oh, shut up, Crow.
- You know,
I could have cocoa,
and we could spin
our Jerry Reed albums.
- Nah. Let's just give
it a little thought.
We’ll be right back.
- Turn it off!
Turn it off!
- We could play splatball
down in the loading bay.
- Uh, maybe.
- What? Can't a guy even have
a couple of drinks to celebrate?
What’s the matter with you guys?
- Is Captain Goodrich in?
- Yes, Lieutenant,
I'll tell him you're here.
- Say, lady.
Just like today,
the rest of the guys
were having a couple of drinks
during Mardi Gras.
- Course, Officer,
he’s not drunk.
- I am, too.
- Is this your liver?
- Otherwise, you wouldn't have
been able to take this
away from me so nimbly.
If I were drunk, I wouldn’t have
been able to take it back.
- Captain Goodrich
will see you now.
- Thank you.
Officer, book him.
- Why is he taking orders
from a crossing guard?
- Hmm...Yes, I am
the police chief of France,
Vichy New Orleans.
- Oh, that mob out there is
really something.
- A little above and
beyond the line of duty, hmm?
- It certainly is.
- Give us a kiss.
- So's your plan, Lee.
- It might work, Captain.
- You do realize
if it doesn't work
what's likely to happen to you?
- Yes, sir.
But the longer we do nothing,
the harder it is
on the police department.
- People are critical.
We’ve gone through that before.
- The Nardo diamonds have been
missing for three years.
- The Nardo men died
in the electric chair,
and their women are in prison.
- Where the diamonds
are nobody knows.
- Yes.
Probably 'cause
their idea's on empty.
- Seems to me,
we have to find them.
- Duh!
- Lee, you're probably
the finest police woman
I’ve ever known.
- Oh, pshaw!
- You’re right,
and your plan’s right.
Josie Nardo
and those other girls
are bound to know
where the diamonds are.
- Of course, they do.
- So if we put you in prison,
you escape
with the Nardo girls,
you’ll know
where the diamonds are.
I think you’ll stick around
and tell us what you find out.
- You flatter me, sir.
- What do you think you ought to
send me to jail for?
- Bravery.
- And sweet love
beyond the call of duty.
- But, sir,
what does this have to do
with the whole
Touch Conners thing?
- ...with the Nardo girls
on the second floor.
- Any electric alarms
on the windows?
- No.
- That's extra.
- The fence is here
in a direct line.
- ♪ Lovely Rita meter maid ♪
- Car right here
in front of the trees.
- Every night?
- Every night.
You pick your
own time of departure.
- Sooner the better.
- There's got to be shooting,
Lee. We'll miss.
- I hope so.
- And you’ve got to be pursued,
unsuccessfully, of course.
- Story of my life, sir.
- I'll give you
all the protection I can,
but we’ve got to be careful.
The slightest suspicion,
they’ll kill you.
- Yes, sir.
- Well, can I drive
you to jail?
- Sergeant Morrison
will take you
to the prison tomorrow morning.
- Thank you, sir.
- And I have to get back
to my ship.
- You’re taking
on a mighty big job, Lee.
- I guess I can't resist
my share of the diamonds, huh?
- Good luck. Good-bye.
- Good-bye, sir.
- So no kiss, huh?
- Hey, looks
like a Catholic grade school.
- Our Lady of French Guiana
from which there is no escape.
- [ speaks French ]
- Will you get
out of my way,
or do I have to beat
you out of here?
- Yeah, Beverly, go get her!
- Aw, leave her alone.
- Stay out of this!
- Leave her alone!
- She got in my way!
- Want to knock somebody around,
try your own size.
- Like who?
- Me.
- Hey, that does make
a lot more sense.
- Why don’t you shut up?
- It’s Lucy and Viv
in the big house.
- Welcome to Dye Job Theater.
- Well, if you two ain’t
a sight for sore eyes.
- They’re all doing
a nickel at UPS.
- I don’t know about your eyes,
but I sure got a sore back.
- Not from working.
- Whoa!
- What's up, Josie?
- I just thought
I'd drop around.
- Get yourself put in the brig
for being down here.
- They made me a trustee.
- Huh!
- Typical.
- I got a new roommate.
- Name's Leona.
- They sure like to make trouble
for us, don’t they?
- She’s crazier than a bedbug.
- How can you tell?
- She’s only
been here three hours.
She wants to go
over the wall.
- Huh. Don’t sound
so crazy to me.
- Well, we let
her go over the wall,
they shoot her,
and we’re...
- Oh, yes, that's what
we'll end up doing.
- [ speaking indistinctly ]
- Huh?
- Guys, it’s
a prison slumber party.
- Yeah, they use razors
in the pillows
for the pillow fights.
- Okay, I’m a cop.
Don't hurt me.
- When moms go bad.
- Move it.
- Shut up.
- Oh, both of you shut up.
- They’re all strung out
on Correctol.
- Don’t you know we’re very hard
to get along with?
- Well, I wasn’t thinking
of have a pleasure trip.
- Oh, what were you
thinking of, suicide?
- No, you have to guess.
- The Nardo diamonds.
- Wouldn’t you just like to get
your hands on them?
- Wouldn’t you?
- Look, we’ve been in here
for three lousy years.
What makes you think right away
you can crash this joint?
- Well, I did something
you three girls didn’t do.
- She was deloused.
- Man, I didn’t think
we missed nothing.
- Such as what?
- On my way in,
I planned a way out.
- Oh, we should have done that.
[ bell rings ]
- Which twin has the Toni?
- Cool it, the RA’s coming!
- A prison filled
with Wendy Darlings.
- Bring me that case of tea.
- And the head
of Alfredo Garcia.
- A true story of Land’s End.
- What makes you so sure
we’ll split with you?
- What makes you sure
that I’ll take you with me?
- Anyway, be quiet
about our secret plan!
- She’ll be there.
- Who’s putting it there?
- None of your business.
- Well, who else will be there?
Can I bring Susan
from cellblock 8?
- Boy,
she sure thinks she’s hot.
- I think she is, too,
if she can get us out of here.
- Sales have gone up
since she’s been here.
- Back now
to Vinyl Window Theater.
- See? They come apart,
but keep it a secret!
- We’ve been doing
a little planning, too.
- It’s a long drop.
- What’s the matter?
No guts?
- Takes more than guts.
- Still, it does take guts.
- We need your car.
- How much
are the diamonds worth?
- Any fence
will give us 200 grand.
- Can you find them?
- I can find them.
- I get 50 grand.
- Yeah, 50 grand.
- So, if you ever have to leave,
that’s how you do it.
- We get there...
- And back.
- It's morning in Joliet.
[ imitating birds whistling ]
- I can hardly sleep.
How about you?
I’m so excited.
We’re going to be the first ones
in line for the scrambled eggs!
- Hooray!
- Wait a minute,
it worked yesterday.
I don’t know what happened.
- Well, it was loose,
so I welded it back.
- These women
are actually escaping
in Easy Spirit dress pumps.
- [ imitating Colonel Klink ]
No one has ever escaped
from Stalag 13!
- Of course not.
- Tell me, boy,
what day is it?
- It’s Christmas day, sir.
- What’s with
the Get Smart music?
- Okay, let’s go.
Aaah!
Aah!
- Don’t forget to bring me
a Dove Bar!
- This is riveting.
- Mm-hmm.
- Bombs away!
- Wait, we can’t leave.
They’re having
creamed corn today.
- Why am I thinking
of Joe Theismann?
[ alarm bells ringing ]
- I hit the bell on my way out!
I hope that’s okay!
[ sirens ]
- [ shouting German-accented
gibberish ]
- Sounds like the Foley artists
are chasing us!
Let’s hit it!
- The Kids in the Hall escaped
from prison!
- [ shouting
Russian-accented gibberish ]
Schnell!
- Hey, let’s take this one.
This one's nice.
- This car
is so convenient.
- Oh, and it’s so roomy.
This is a nice car.
- Ooh, and so clean.
- Floor mats and everything.
It's got that new car smell.
- ♪ Oh-ho,
the Wells Fargo wagon-- ♪
- [ police sirens ]
- Look out!
[ gunshots ]
- Boy, I sure do wish
I had a gun.
- Ow! Take it easy!
- What’s the matter?
- Watch my arm, that's what.
- Oh, that's tough.
- Watch that turn.
- That one?
- Ladies, it’s a big car.
You can spread out a little.
- Where do we go from here?
- We're losing them!
- Turn left half a mile up.
- I’m up
for something chickeny.
- Louie Blanc?
- Yeah.
- Hey, you think he'll give us
something decent
to wear and some lipstick?
- Good enough
for where we’re going.
- They've given up.
Boy, I sure do wish
I could have taken
a couple shots at them.
- Hey, and a couple of shots,
a couple of shots...
[ speaking like auctioneer ]
- He will if he knows
what’s good for him.
- How long do you think
it’s going to take us, Josie?
- Oh, took a couple of days
with the boys.
I don’t see how
we can do much better.
- On foot?
- In these shoes?
- On foot, it’d take
about a couple of years.
- Louie will give us a boat.
We got a few things
on Louie.
- Yeah, we saw him coming out
of Lend Me a Tenor.
[ tires squealing ]
- I’m spritzing.
Any of you mugs
got a problem with that?
- What’s on your mind?
- Nobody has any guns yet.
- [ doing auctioneer call ]
- If it weren't for me,
you'd all rot in jail.
I want to make sure
I get that 50 grand.
- We keep bargains.
- I just thought I’d tell you.
- Hi.
- I’m a good shot.
If you try anything,
I’ll kill all three of you.
- And if you try something...
- We’ll kill you.
- Well, I guess
I had that coming.
- Now that we’ve bonded
let’s go.
- Well, this is going
to be fun. Oh!
- Honey.
- Shut up, Iris.
- It’s lovely.
- Yeah, it’s great, isn’t it?
- Just lovely.
- Yeah, I’m going to dredge it
and put up condos.
- But then, of course,
after you got
a few little ol' oil wells,
you wouldn’t have to spend
any time in a nasty jungle.
- Uh, what’s that?
Hold on.
I got a big wax ball up here.
There.
- No, I guess not.
- Nice little scene.
Oh, the two plots are
on a collision course.
- Really a great time
to spring a leak.
- If I ever see that lousy Louie
again, I’ll break his neck.
- Josie, what do we do now?
- Hitch a ride, I guess.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- We don’t have to do anything!
Here comes Touch Conners!
- Oh.
- Hey, look over there.
- Young girls
in primary colors.
- Come on over here!
- Get over here! We just want
to kill you for a minute!
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Come on!
- Cut it, I said.
- Let go of the boat.
- What's your problem, girls?
- Bob, honey, I'm frightened
What do they want?
- Just the boat.
Pull it into shore.
- Now, wait a minute.
What do you think this is?
- Uncle Charlie, no!
- [ gunshot ]
- Steve, Chip, Ernie!
[ blubbing ]
- Oh!
- What’s the matter with you?
Are you crazy?
- ♪ Da dun da dun ♪
Save yourself!
- You’re no Mannix
to me, mister!
- Oh, I’m binding.
Can't you tell I'm binding?
- Oh, man, he landed
right on the wax worms.
- Um, sorry
about Mr. Demarest.
- You were in prison?
Do you know Bubba?
- What’s this?
Touch Conners is being helped
from the field,
but he should return
in the second half.
[ imitating crowd cheering ]
- Splashing water all over me!
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, owie, oh!
- What’s your dream?
- It’s love!
- What’s the matter?
- Oh, my fantasy!
Oh. Nope,
she can’t take it there.
She can’t take it there.
- Come on, break it up!
- We’ve got guests!
- What’s the matter?
- That guy tried to conk me
over the head with an oar,
and I shot him,
and she jumped me!
- Now, hold it.
- You both came to see me.
That's the first step.
- There shouldn’t be
any shooting.
- What’s the matter,
you chicken?
- In case you want to know,
shots make noise,
and noise carries.
- Ooh.
- There's no reason
why we should attract
any more attention
than we have to.
- Says who?
- She's got a point.
Now quit the fighting.
Give her back her gun.
- Who wants guns?
- I do, I do!
- No hard feelings.
- That's what you think.
- That’s what I think.
- Do you like Elly Mae?
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Ow...ow...owie.
Ohh.
- Hello, breakfast.
- Well, we caught it,
but what is it?
- You could have killed him.
- Well, we didn’t, did we?
- Oh, we should have.
- I didn’t see much else
we can do.
- Oh, just wait
till he wakes up.
He won’t know what hit him.
- But what’s the pelt worth?
- Maybe I better not.
- Oh, hold it.
- Will you let me alone?
- You’re crazy for that gun.
- Knock it off.
- She just wants to kill
somebody, doesn't she?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, hold them both
as hostages.
- Have you held
your hostage today?
- We got a long trip
ahead of us.
We might run into trouble.
I’d like something to bargain
with, and they'd do.
- Diamonds and guns ain’t enough
of a bargain?
- ♪ Diamonds and guns ♪
- Oh, get it yourself.
- She’s right.
We better tie him up.
Go on, hurry there.
- I got a little poem.
- Kind of go for him.
- Nice enough looking.
- Stupid name, though.
- I call it the mid-section.
- Wonder who he is?
- Poor little guy.
I think he's lost.
- Couldn’t be a friend of yours,
could he?
- You know, I got a feeling you
don’t like me.
- Hey, I’m not dreaming.
- You okay?
- I guess so.
What’s the story?
- Enchanted April
meets Deliverance.
- Man, don’t you read
the papers?
- Once in a while.
- Ever heard
of the Nardo gang?
- Yeah. Said they’re
a pretty rough group.
- You just remember that.
- Oh, thank you very much!
- Okay, Red.
- Oh, Bob, honey.
What are they going to do?
- Shut up.
- Thanks, White.
- She's got a good question.
- [ woman crying ]
What are you going to do?
- Stick around,
then you’ll know, too.
- Ooh.
- Kidnapping maybe?
- If you’re lucky.
- What’s your name?
- Bob.
- Okay, it's Fred!
- Bob Matthews.
Not worth much
in this kidnapping game.
- Yeah, that’s
very discouraging.
That your wife?
- No.
- No, no, no, no.
- A friend.
- Some friend.
- Look, if you don't stop
your crying,
I’ll give you something
to cry about.
- My dad used to say that.
- Yeah, one more girl
we don’t need.
- What can I do for you?
- Can you get us
Peggy’s autograph?
- We had a leaky boat
with no motor.
Anyway,
we like yours better.
- So you’re off
on a cruise, huh?
- Yeah.
- Sounds fun.
- Why’d you have
to kill the guide?
- For effect.
- Self-defense.
- Er...I had one other thing
I was going to ask.
- Well, come on.
Let's get going.
- Okay.
[ grunts ]
♪ Da dum da dum da dum ♪
- Head upstream,
keep her down the middle.
- Okay.
And what would you say
is the load limit
for this thing?
- Listen, we got to have
this boat back in an hour.
I left my license.
- Do you guys think
it's possible
that the Video Watchdog people
are wrong
and that Corman really is
a terrible director?
- [ screams ]
- God, you scared me!
- What is that?
- Oh, sit down.
It's just an alligator.
- Just an alligator?
- Boy, we’re having more fun
than I thought!
- GAF View-Master
presents the Okefenokee.
- I think they’re headed
for Doug Kershaw’s place.
- ♪ Spanish moss,
the land of the Chia ♪
- I wonder what other names
Touch Conners considered
before he hit on Touch?
- Thrust?
- Jab?
- Punch
- Crunch?
- Splat.
- Smidge.
- Shout.
- Batch.
- Um, Scrub.
- Flake.
- Wink.
- Sploot?
- Josie, how much further
we got to go?
- Just till we find
a dry spot to land.
- Hey, look at that!
[ birds squawking ]
- Ah, Uganda.
- Hey, you son of a gun,
gonna have big fun.
- Bob, what's happening?
- Not much,
how about with you?
- Well, my chest
has fallen asleep.
- Don’t worry, honey.
It'll be all right.
- That’s very sweet.
- Sure, you can use it.
- Red, you talk too much.
Oh, cut it out.
- Beverly can sure handle
a Johnson, can’t she?
- Yes, she can.
- Mm-hmm.
- That looks like dry ground.
We can camp over there.
- It sure ain’t no palace.
- It ain’t no prison,
either.
- It’s sort of in the middle.
- Get out and pull the boat in.
- "Billie, do this,
Billie, do that."
- You heard me.
- And remember, try not to kill
anyone this time.
- Pinch Conners?
- Probe Conners.
- Hmm.
- Wing Conners?
- Hmm, Mike.
- Are you complaining?
- Man, you know I am.
- I’m a good person.
I'm a great guy.
I got a lot to offer.
This'll be fun.
I’m a good person.
I'm a great guy.
I got a lot to offer.
This'll be fun.
I'm a good person.
I'm a great guy!
- Okay, okay, Tom.
Okay, Tom, you're sounding
real confident.
I think it's time for you
to call up Gypsy
and ask her on that date.
Here, I’ll press speed dial
for you.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Hey, Joel, Tom.
[ phone dialing ]
- Tom's just about to ask Gypsy
out on a date,
and I told him you and I would
set up a scavenger sale
like we saw
in the dating short.
- Isn’t that
a little weird, Joel?
- Yeah, it is. Here, I'll
put it on the speakerphone.
- I’m a guy.
I'm a great person.
[ line ringing ]
- What are you going
to say, huh?
What are you going to say?
What are you going to ask her?
What if she doesn’t like you?
What are you going to do?
I don't think she likes you.
- Hello?
Hello?
- Hello, uh...
Hello, uh, Gypsy?
- Yes, what is it?
I’m really kind of eating.
- Um, th-this is Tom.
- Who?
- Uh, Tom Servo.
I stand next to you
on the Satellite of Love?
- Oh. Oh, the red one.
- See? She remembers you.
- What do you want?
- Go for it, baby.
- Well, there’s
this scavenger sale.
- What’s that?
- Well, it's just
a scavenger scale--sale,
and I was wondering if maybe you
might want to go with me
to this scavenger scale?
Sale.
- Why would I want to do that?
- Um, so, anyway,
you want to go?
- No.
- Great!
- I said no.
- Please?
- No.
I'll say please 10,000 times.
Please, please, please.
- Oh, okay.
But we leave when I say.
- Oh, great!
Okay, see you then.
Bye-bye, honey.
[ laughing ]
- All right.
- Well, fellas,
you can tell right away
when something like that’s
going to go real smooth.
In fact, you know what?
- You’re a good person.
- I’m a good person.
- You’ve got a lot to offer.
- I’ve got a lot to offer.
- You’re red!
- I'm red!
- He’s red!
- [ alarms sounding ]
[ all shouting ]
- And your arms don't work.
- And my arms don't--
Hey!
- Sure wish she'd shut up.
- [ woman crying ]
- Oh, she’s not hurting you.
Hand me the salt.
- I set up
the volleyball net.
- ...if I say she is,
and she gives me a pain.
- Where’d they get the ladles
and the spices?
- Alligator’s back there.
- Big one?
- No, they're tiny.
- Well, I wouldn't
like to stick my foot
on top of one in the dark.
- This about ready?
- In a few minutes.
- Well, just stand here
and jut some more.
- Josie, how much longer
you figure
it’ll take us to get there?
- Oh, a couple of days,
day and a half if we’re lucky
- Leech look appetizing.
- Man,
I hope I live long enough
to get my hands
on them diamonds.
- Well, they sure are
holding us up plenty.
- They may be worth it.
- For what?
- We'll see.
- Aw, "We’ll see, we’ll see."
- Look, if I bother you,
go somewhere else.
- ♪ Da da duh da da ♪
- Oh, cut it!
Cut it, I said!
- By God,
I'll kill that dame!
- You’re killing nobody!
Now stop it!
- Some of us aren’t going to get
out of here alive.
- Oh, really, who?
Oh, me.
- Food’s ready, unless
you’d rather fight than eat.
- Aw, shut up.
- Well, this is going to be
a great dinner.
- You know, I feel less
like a hostage
and more like a friend.
- Take this over to them.
- What if we don’t have enough?
- We got enough.
- There’s plenty of squirrel
to go around.
- [ crying ]
- Oh, that dame makes me sick.
- Okay, who had the Granny’s
Country Omelet with?
Oh, you need coffee?
- Please, I want to talk to you.
- Talk to yourself.
- Oh, oh! You’re kneeling
on Little Touch.
- Well, what do I do now?
Feed him?
- Why not?
- Does he need changing?
- Untie his hands
till he’s through.
- Mmm.
Really great grub.
- [ crying ] Really great grub,
yum, yum.
- Uh, honey,
will you pass the salt?
- Mm.
- You know, I've
always heard bad things
about being held hostage.
- Jab Conners?
- Grunt Conners?
- Link.
- Enjoy yourself.
- I just did.
- What’s for dessert?
- Tuna wiggle.
- Come on,
what’s for dessert?
Aren't we even
having dessert?
- Boy, you just can’t keep away
from him, can you?
- Better than not being able
to get near him.
- Who'd like a drink?
- Man, who wouldn’t?
- I’ll have a Rob Roy.
- Take a look
in my blanket over there.
- You’re kidding!
- Oh, those kids, I’ve never
seen them so happy.
- It’s not enough
to slow us up tomorrow.
- It doesn’t get
any skuzzier than this.
- Four years is
a long time to be in the jug.
- Oww!
- She was in the jug?
- Hey, give me some,
too, you pig.
- Hey, come on,
bring it over here!
- [ laughs ] After a prison
break and hostage taking,
it’s back to the lodge
for a smooth Canadian Club.
- Oh, no!
- Oh! Oh!
- Oh, Josie, this is crazy.
- So it’s crazy.
- Nardo girls never run around
in pants like a bunch of boys.
- What, they get drunk
and they make shorts?
- Yeah,
they’re Daisy Mae shorts.
- Mmm.
- Hey, Vera, I want mine cut off
a little shorter.
- Do it yourself.
- The purpose of the movie
finally revealed.
- [ calling ] Oh, Touch?
- Maybe he goes for girls
in little blue sweaters.
- Ah, maybe, sure.
Um, hmm...
- Please leave me alone!
- These are stirrup pants!
I beg you!
- I’ll give you anything.
- Like what?
- Listen to me.
Just get me out of here, honey,
and I’ll give you
whatever you want.
- How much?
- Whatever you want.
- I want
your sleeveless blue dress.
- A thousand? 10.
- And your boyfriend,
you buying him, too?
- I don’t care.
Just get me out of here.
My daddy will give you
whatever you want.
- Hear that, handsome?
Your girlfriend's trying
to buy her way out,
but she doesn’t care
what happens to you.
- Yes, I did.
Thank you .
- Isn't that right?
- A little off the sides.
- Get me out of here!
- Oh, I wouldn’t wear your lousy
sweater if you gave it to me!
- [ crying ]
- Nice kid.
Sell her man
right down the river.
- Yeah, some women
have no class.
- I sure miss Nicky.
- Yeah. Who’s Nicky?
- Joey, Mike.
- You can just forget
about missing Mike.
- Would we have a ball
with those diamonds
if the guys were
still with us?
- No. Yes.
- I plan to have a ball
without them.
I'm going to go
down to Mexico,
and I’m going to buy myself
a town.
- Huh?
- You’re drunk.
What do you want with a town?
- Well, you’d always have
a place to park.
- I may be drunk,
but I'm going to buy a town,
I'm going to buy
everybody in it,
and I’m going to order them
around the rest of my life.
- Why, don’t you have goals?
- You got a better idea?
- I got a better idea.
- I’m going
to start a sod farm.
- Going to find me a doctor
and have him change
my whole face around.
- To the back.
- Cut it up.
- You ain’t that ugly.
- I ain’t ugly at all,
and you know it.
But I ain’t going to look
like me no more.
- I'm going to look
like Tito Puente.
- I'm going to keep
the old little address book,
and I'm going to start
with the judge first
who sent the guys
to the chair.
- Did they all go
to the same chair?
- Then all the folks
of the jury,
and I'm going
to louse them all up.
- How do you mean?
- Going to break up
all their happy homes.
- Boy, she really slides
into her sentences, doesn’t she?
- Going to make
their wives hate them,
and their kids.
- Well, I’ll do something
to their kids.
- I’m going
to louse them all up!
[ laughing ]
- I’m still
with the town idea.
- Good for you.
- What are you going
to do, Josie?
- Mm, same thing.
- I tell you, I got a plan.
I'm going to get me a big house
south of the border,
and I’m going to rent rooms
to everybody that’s on the lam.
- The old lady in the shoe.
- Sure, why not?
I figure I can make
a good living
and make plenty of trouble
for the cops at the same time.
- I’m going to star
in The Mothers-in-Law.
- I hope to make detective--
Ooh!
- I just want to be by myself,
that’s all.
- A lone wolf.
- Awoo!
- You can’t trust them.
- Now, come on,
we were having a good time!
- Touch, how about you?
- Girls, let’s do this
again sometime.
- Mmm, 10W-40.
Well, it's good, though.
- I’ll take the first watch.
Guess he’s
not going anyplace.
Thanks for the drink.
- Sure can hold plenty
of it.
- You don’t do
so bad yourself.
- Want to take that across
the street and get deposit?
- I love you, Sir Booze.
Bye-bye.
[ all making vomiting noises ]
- Oh, God,
what did we do last night?
What was in that stuff?
[ vomiting noises ]
- Oh, no, they forgot
to hang the hostages
10 feet off the ground.
- [ snoring] Hiccup!
[ snoring ]
- Okay, who’s for lizard
biscuits with cypress gravy?
- Hmm?
- Hey!
- What?
Oh, I’ve been shot, okay.
- She’s at the Y.
- Help! Help!
- What on...?
- I don’t think she can swim.
- Wait a minute,
I'll swim out here
and ask her if she can swim.
- [ imitating
sound of speedboat ]
- Help!
- Just stand up!
You're in the shallow end!
- [ imitating engine revving ]
- By the boat.
- I see him.
It’s going to get her!
- Quick, Josie,
cut me loose!
- [ gasping ]
- [ humming along
with dramatic music ]
- Wait, how’s he going to get
to the pool where she is?
- Help! Help!
- I’m a-comin',
I’m a-comin'.
- Oh, help!
- Wait, that’s a mud puppy!
- If only David Hasselhoff
were here!
- [ humming along
with dramatic music ]
- Oh, that’s a problem.
I'll go report in.
- Boy, I can’t wait until
all these movies come together.
- Mmm, think of it.
- You know, it's hard to keep
your head above water
when you’re up to your ass
in alligators.
- I got a poster like that.
- I’ve got him!
No, no, help!
Blub blub blub!
- So you want to make shoes
out of me, huh?
I got your shoes right here.
- Well, wait a minute.
Didn't we forget--
Oh, my girlfriend!
- She was
in a pool across town.
They couldn’t
have saved her anyway.
- So, uh, what
are you doing next Saturday?
Give you a lift?
- Hey, it’s
a wet Pendleton contest.
- She’s a man!
- Uh-oh.
- Huh?
- I'm sorry.
- Apology accepted.
- Yeah.
- Oh, man,
wish you hadn’t done that.
- Sorry for what?
- Sorry for not saving
her life.
- Oh, her.
It was a first date.
- Making you risk your life.
- Was that supposed
to be a moment?
- Yeah.
- Hey, the boat handles
real well now!
Making good time, too!
- Yes, every available man.
I want
that entire area surrounded.
- Oui, mon capitaine.
- Any man that gets too close,
I’ll personally break him.
- Way to be.
- Try anything,
Lieutenant Hampton's through.
- Hey, they traded up.
- Oh, they got hats
and everything.
- Chief?
- Yeah.
- Wait, didn’t
I just talk to you?
- No, only one helicopter.
Personally tell the pilot
not to get too close.
He mustn’t hover
over the scene.
- Now, wait, wait,
I have no idea.
Wait a minute.
I didn't order this.
I meant to put you on hold.
- What’s the matter with
that unit on the left?
All right, pull them back!
We must not risk being seen!
- Allez!
- Milk! Milk!
Get your 2%, get your butter,
sticks or patties!
Milk!
- Josie, how many more thousand
miles we got to go?
- About five more miles.
It's rough. I don’t want
to try it at night.
We’ll stop
at the first good place.
- Are you sure
you can find them?
- You could blindfold me,
and I could find them.
- There’s an extra leg
in there.
- Still gonna find some help
spending the loot.
- If Nicky was here,
he'd be ordering you around
just like he always did.
- You know what? I miss being
told what to do.
Oh, that looks
like a good place.
We’ll pull in there.
- Okay, now,
remember our rule--
only one dead at each place.
- Hey,
if they got drunk again,
they won’t have any pants
left at all.
- Drink, drink, drink, drink!
- So far, so good.
Nobody dead yet.
- Still beats the prison.
- Josie, if the cops
are waiting for us,
how do you figure we’re going
to get the diamonds out of here?
- Take a powder.
- Sure I can’t help you?
- I think we can manage
without you. Get lost.
- Well, I’ll see you
at lunch then.
I’m outta here.
- Too bad. Nice guy.
- Huh! He’s nothing.
- Hey, any chance
for a drink of water?
- I’ll get him some.
- Oh, excuse me, miss.
Come to
the Church in the Wildwood.
- I thirst.
- Have a drink.
- Don’t mind if I do.
- Oh, good, 'cause
that’s what’s happening.
- I don’t get it.
- It’s just water.
- You will.
- Just what is it with you?
- Stuff.
- Thanks.
- Water?
- We got to get the wood
before it gets dark.
- I’ll get some.
- Oh, hi.
- Not you again.
We can't keep doing this.
- Why don’t you tell me
the story of your life?
- Before I went into crime?
- You were never in it.
- Well, don’t tell my friends.
Are you all right?
- Oh, sure, just great.
- Wrists sore?
- Not too sore.
- So how
have your stools been?
Mmph mmph!
- Try that again,
and I’ll kill you!
- Now what’s going on?
- Oh, I was just checking
his rope for the night,
and he tried to get fresh.
- You sure it wasn’t your idea?
- I’m sure.
- Next time,
we kidnap Ernest Borgnine.
- How’s that?
- You didn’t have to cut
off his hands.
- Hi, what’s up?
- Cut it out, you two.
- I think there’s too many cooks
in the kitchen.
- I always notice you’re around
to protect him.
- So what?
- So I don’t like it,
that’s all.
I think there’s something
between them.
- Yeah, see?
Something between them.
- That's no rule.
- Girls, plenty of Touch
to go around.
- That gripes me.
- Well, knock it off
and let’s get some shuteye.
- Yeah, sure, warden.
You kind of go for that dame,
don’t you?
- Bother you, Red?
- It’s orange, not red!
- I wouldn’t.
- What? What?
- Can’t get enough
of that shot.
- Hey, who TP’d the swamp?
[ piano music ]
- ♪ As time goes on... ♪
- Keep any eye out
for gators, will you?
I’d like to get out of here
with the same pieces I got in.
- Well, that could be improved.
- Yeah, says who?
- Hey, isn't Vera coming in?
- Nah. She’s still asleep.
She must think we’re working.
- Whoa, hold on.
[ chuckling ]
- After we left clam flowage
that day,
we knew that one day soon
we would return
to seek
the wily bucketmouth.
Next up, Myrna
with a new carp-ball recipe.
- Do not bring
your padding here.
- Looks like the bayou’s
all clogged up.
- Hmm? Hmm.
- Hey!
- Rog?
- Hey, Roger’s getting footage
for another movie.
- Uh, Rog, over here, buddy.
Rog? Uh, Rog?
Roger!
Roger, would you please
cut with the thing?
- Man, what do we do now?
- It sure wasn’t this way
the last time.
- No, but it sure is now.
- They got a flat?
- Do we have to go
through this stuff?
- Right down the middle.
- Why can't we go around?
- And take a chance
on getting lost?
We could be wandering
around this mess
for the rest of our lives,
which wouldn’t be long.
- Looks like this stuff
will catch on the propeller.
Do we have
to row through this?
- Stop fighting!
Just stop fighting!
- All right, how we going
to get through this mess?
- We’ll pull
ourselves through.
It’s only
a couple of feet deep.
We’ll take turns.
- At Touch.
- Uh, will you
send this paddle?
Oooh-oh!
- How long’s it going to take us
to get through, Josie?
- Aw, how do I know?
All I know
is there’s no other way.
- Giddy up. Ha ha.
Just kidding, girls.
- Hey, don’t go to sleep
on the job!
- Vera, shut up.
- [ crying ] Why can’t we
just joke anymore?
- Oh, you two take a turn.
- Maybe they should
all just walk.
- Nice work, huh?
- Yeah.
- Wait a minute,
this is an actual trick.
This hasn’t even been edited.
- This calls for
not taking any chances.
We keep his hands tied.
- Chinese fire drill!
- Don't make
a lot of sense to me
why we should do all the work.
- Oh, this stinking
swamp water stinks!
- Oh, that’s Touch.
- Why don’t you two stop griping
and get to work?
- Give me that paddle!
I want the thing part of it!
- Give me that!
I want the wide end!
- I want the thin part
of the paddle!
- I'm gonna smack you!
- ♪ Old man river ♪
- Look,
it’s clear water up ahead.
- Huh? Credence Clearwater
up ahead?
- No, no.
- And Canned Heat?
- ♪ Goin' up country ♪
♪ Don't you wanna go? ♪
- Well, that scene
was really important.
- As crises go,
that wasn’t that bad.
- As we left
the clam flowage that day,
we knew that one day soon
we would return
to seek
the wily bucketmouth.
Did I just say that?
- Yeah.
- They're swamp diamonds
'cause on account of the fact
they’re looking for diamonds
that are hidden in the...
- Swamp.
- Wouldn't it be funny
if it just turned out
to be swamp cubic zirconia?
- Mm, no.
- This is really
The Neverending Story.
- How’s by you?
- Fine!
[ somber brass playing ]
- Herb Alpert plays the haunting
Swamp Diamond love theme.
- [ sighs ]
I could use an overdose
of Dramamine right now.
- Mm-hmm.
- Journey
to the beginning of time!
- You know, sometimes it's
just nice to look at the scenery
and just not talk.
- Mmm.
- Right here.
- Man, I thought we were
never going to make it!
- Gee, I sure can’t wait to get
my hands on those diamonds!
- They must be
at a Stuckey's.
- Barely more sophisticated
than To Catch a Thief,
but still pretty good.
- I guess we steered
to the right spot.
- What are they,
digging for a six-pack
of Lone Star or something?
- It’s in the boat.
- Hey, bring me a shovel!
- Shovel coming up!
- Hey, how long you been here?
- Ropes cutting your wrists?
- What wrists?
- What bris?
- I wish I could untie you.
- I wish you could, too.
- Hurry up!
- If I wasn’t tied,
we could jump them now.
- Or you could all jump me.
- What makes you think
I want to?
- You do.
- Am I that transparent?
- If one of us were wounded,
we’d never get
out of here alive.
- Why don't you let me in
on the secret?
- Come on,
where’s the shovel?
- I’m just
an average American crook.
Josie’s watching.
Found the shovel!
- I had to look
all over the boat for it!
- Here’s the shovel!
- I feel something!
It’s right here!
I can feel it!
- Watch out with that thing!
- Aw, who needs it?
- Hey, I worked hard
for that shovel!
- I've got it.
- That straw’s hard to move.
- Mm-hmm.
- Watch it now.
- Wait a minute, why did they
bury a Realistic clock radio?
- Man,
that’s what I’m here for.
- Oh, you and me both.
- Well, open it, Josie!
Open it up here!
- I’ll do it.
- Now, hold it!
You want to get the thing?
- Oh, smart,
ever heard of ricochet?
- They’re shooting it
execution-style! Oh!
- You got it.
- Oh, I hope they didn’t kill
the diamonds.
- Oh, wait a minute.
Hold it.
- But first, a prayer.
- ♪ Peace on earth
was all it said ♪
- It’s a Ronco stud setter?
- Too bad you couldn't
bring yourself
to do a quarter
of the digging.
- That was uncalled for.
- Oh, man,
it’s raining diamonds!
- Uh, not a good idea.
- Oh, you can cut it out
knocking me around
now that I’m rich!
- You're asking for it!
- Oh! [ laughs ]
She’s always looking for
a reason to wrestle, that one.
- Dream on.
- It’s Haley Mills and
Hayley Mills in The Misfits.
[ both grunting ]
- Suddenly,
it’s spore wrestling.
- This is better
than getting slapped!
- Hey, it’s a reenactment
of the breakup of the Judds.
- Yes, it's Delta Burke
and Linda Bloodworth Thomason
squaring off.
- You know,
I think this is really
about more
than just diamonds.
- Whoo, ouch.
- You usually find this
sort of thing on pay-per-view.
- Man, all you can eat
and a show.
- Ooh, ooh!
- Now, cut it out.
- Hey, Beverly Garland's bra.
[ whispers ]
I've seen the bra.
- Now stop it
or I’ll pound both of you!
- I've loaded the trap
with perm solution!
- Vera, get these things
in the boat.
- Oh, she had to use
the diamonds for fuel.
- We better tie you up again.
- Okay!
- Getting to feel natural.
- You know, you’re
not such a bad guy.
- You’re okay yourself,
Josie.
- Too bad you’re so square.
I never could figure
you legit guys.
- Guess I was
just brought up wrong.
- He’s getting good
at bringing that on.
- I don’t like to be laughed at.
- What’s the matter?
- Oh, just his mouth.
- Do you have to hit him
when his hands are tied?
- I’d hate to hit him
when they wasn’t.
- Oh, good point.
- Let’s get going.
- That’s two for me.
- Man, I’d like to get out
of this dump.
- Man, where did they
get all that stuff?
Are they the Howells?
- Hey, Josie, you figure
they got the swamp
surrounded looking for us?
- Oh, they'll surround us
all right,
but they got a big area
to surround.
We’ll get out of here,
unless you want to stay here.
- Now, part two,
the trip home.
- No!
- Hey, can we stop
and wrestle now?
- What am I thinking?
I got to get ready
for my big date.
What am I going to do?
I got to get my blazer out.
- All right, got you.
- Not much farther, honey.
- So you see, I'm the muscular
one on the left
who makes a lot of
the intellectual type comments.
You know, they actually had
to widen my seat
because my shoulders kept
hitting Joel?
- Really?
I don't remember that.
- Well, of course,
I monitor myself
so as not to make
the others look bad.
Nice fellas and all,
but you understand.
- But, Tom, we better get along
on the date part.
I’ve only set aside
about two more minutes.
- Uh-huh. Yeah, neat.
You know, it's so refreshing
to meet someone else
who enjoys the cinema.
You know, I feel people
are hungry
- for intelligent films...
- [ yawning ]
- to talk about
in an intellectual way.
You’ll excuse me for a moment,
won’t you?
- Oh, yeah, whatever.
- ♪ I hear the secrets
that you keep ♪
- Hey, Joel.
- Hi.
- Thanks for setting all
this up. It's really helping,
and I think Gypsy’s really
enjoying herself over there.
- Hey.
- Hey, can you set us up
with a couple of Cokes?
- No problem.
- Oh, and any advice?
- Well, Tom, I'd probably rule
out the possibility
of a second date
if I were you.
- Yeah, I think
it’s going really good, too.
Now, after we leave,
I thought we'd stroll
the Lido deck
under a warm gibbous moon...
figuratively speaking,
of course, and then...
Sandwich.
- Uh, Tom, I think you’d better
check on your date.
- What? Who's--Doh!
- So you want to know
how to make Tom cry?
- [ laughing ]
- Scram!
Uh...heh heh.
Huzzah, fair maiden.
Your prince hath procured
an elixir
fit for only the fairest
of the fair.
- What?
- Uh, Joel brought us
a couple of Cokes.
- Oh, uh, isn’t
that Crow guy funny?
- I suppose so
for the occasional diversion,
but he hardly compares
with the works
of Yeats, Nietzsche,
"Dostoevskety,"
which, of course,
I read every week.
- Oh, right.
Tom, this is really fun,
and your time's up,
but I'm going.
But you should stay and have
fun, okay? Thanks. Bye.
- No, no, I wouldn’t dream
of staying.
I’ll walk you home.
- But Tom,
I only live 10 feet away.
- And I shall walk on air
all the while.
After you, my sweet vision.
- Oh, all right.
- These are the precious years.
We’ll be right back.
- Oh, sorry I’m late.
Date went great.
Excuse me, pardon me.
Tell you about it later.
Hey, Joe Namath. Oh.
- Oop. No pants.
- Oh, she’s going to put
her handgun in water.
- I think she’s doing this
under the cover of day.
- The Gun in Betty Lou’s Fly.
- Was that a Gun In Betty Lou’s
Handbag reference?
- Uh, yeah.
- Got it.
- It's nothin'.
- I’m going to turn
to a life of cri--
Oh, wait.
- Now to put the gun
with the rightful owner.
She’s like the gun fairy.
- Oh, gracious,
they'll all be so surprised
when they wake up and their guns
are all nice and clean.
- But, Santa, why?
Why are you taking my gun?
- Yeah, she’ll probably go eat
all the Nutter Butters, too.
- Yeah.
- While these women sleep,
a pasty film is being made.
So who was Betty Lou?
- Drop her, okay?
- It's okay, Billie.
Go back to sleep.
- Mm, you haven't
grabbed my hair yet.
- Oh, she has an early shift
somewhere, I guess.
- Beverly, stop.
I beg you to think about this.
You’ll never get on
My Three Sons if you do this.
- Well, she's taking
her pignose amp
wherever she’s going.
- Mmm.
- Think I'll leave them
a can of smoked oysters
and some soda crackers.
- Touch? Touch?
♪ Thought I heard you
calling my name now ♪
- What kind of cologne
does he wear?
- Mmph!
[ muffled ]
Gee, your hand smells funny.
- Want to take a trip with me?
- Mmph mmph mmph.
- You might like it
when you got there.
I don’t want to kill you.
- Tmj?
- I really don’t want
to kill you.
I’ve got the diamonds.
- You got the shaft.
- I love diamonds.
- I’m naming myself Touch,
that’s it.
- You come with me
and don’t make a sound.
- Hmm, bullet in the head
or go with the psycho woman?
Tough choice.
- Now, wait why is she taking
him with her?
- She wants it all.
- Oh.
- She wants to taste it all.
- Um, I haven’t had a line
in 10 minutes.
I need a line.
Can I just say a little one?
- Oh, today I’m just going
to sleep in.
- Oh, how long
have I been posing?
- Can someone come over here
and unbunch me?
- Josie!
- Wake the Pussycats!
- What’s the matter?
- They’re gone!
- They got my gun.
- Mine, too.
- The diamonds!
That crazy, sneaky little...
- She took the wax beans!
- The boat.
- Hey, it’s still here.
- Why do you suppose
she didn’t take the boat?
- Too hard to carry.
- Why did she take Bob?
- Couldn’t you see she was
crazy about him?
- But she loved that boat.
- Come on, let’s go.
- Where?
- Well, after her,
where else?
- Now, wait a minute.
Vera's smart,
and she’s clever.
There’s got to be a reason
why she didn’t take that boat.
- In order to catch a girl,
you got to think like a girl.
- Maybe she wanted us
to come running after her.
- You can’t let her get away.
- I’m not about to go running
into a bullet, either.
- I don’t know
how she did it.
- First thing we’ve got to do is
find out where she’s at.
- But how?
- We better see her
before she sees us,
because she’ll kill us.
- Just like that?
Well, I guess the first thing is
to find their trail.
- Well, she left
her curling iron.
She’ll be back,
and we’ll be ready for her.
- [ quacking ]
- Beverly! Beverla-ha-ha!
Oh, I love that one.
- Wait a minute, this tree
wasn’t here before.
- [ whispers ] Josie.
[ all whispering ]
- Shh! Shh!
- You can see
where they went.
- She probably held
a gun on him.
- You can tell a lot
from a leaf.
- Remember, I told you
she wasn't no good.
- It wasn’t exactly
a surprise to me.
Look, if she went through
this mess, I guess we can, too.
Now, remember, if she sees us,
we’re dead, so keep it quiet.
- What if we see her?
- What are we going to do
when we find her?
- Well, it beats me.
- Well,
then why do we have to...
- Oh, let’s do one thing
at a time. Come on.
- Hey, don’t push!
Don't push!
- Don’t you push me!
- Just keep quiet.
- Adirondack chairs.
- Oh, the un-cola man
should be sitting there.
- Wait, there's traces
of Groom & Clean on this bush.
- Maybe we should split up
into groups of one.
Let’s synchronize
your watch.
[ dramatic music ]
[ humming along ]
- Well, at least I look hot.
- You’re real dishy,
you know that?
- How long do we play
this game?
- Until it’s over.
- Oh.
- Behind here.
- I got a way to get us
in there,
and you’re going to lead us.
- How did she ever get up
in that tree?
- She’s going to catapult.
- How did she ever get up there
with all those guns?
- If I know Vera,
she's got them lined up
like a shooting gallery.
- Looks like Bob’s okay.
- I bet she’s got sandwiches
up there, too.
- We could spread out and flush
her from three sides.
- Exactly what she expects
us to do.
- Is she a good shot?
- She can hit anything
she can see.
If we were to rush out there,
we’d all three be dead
before we could reach her.
- Looks kind of like
Jane Russell in The Outlaw.
- Mm-hmm.
- What are we going to do?
- Impose sanctions.
- Now, she figures
that she can shoot us,
but we can’t shoot her.
- And that’s bad
for us, right?
- We’ve got nothing
to shoot her with.
- That's right,
so if we could shoot her,
the surprise would be
on our side.
- Yeah, that’d be
a real surprise, all right.
- Come on, I got an idea.
- Angels,
you're going undercover
at the swimsuit competition.
- What was our plan?
I’m all confused.
- I used to make these
when I was a kid.
Got a couple of rats
with them once.
- Weird childhood.
- Sure hope you can get
one more.
- How far do you think
you can throw it?
- I’m not exactly
the smallest girl in the class.
- Wow, what a range.
- But no trajectory.
- You two girls
circle around,
and then when I whistle
like I told you,
get her to take a shot
at you.
You got to get her to take
a shot at you,
but don’t do it so good
you get yourself killed.
- Uh, what risk
are you taking again?
- I sure hope you can throw
that thing.
- I do, too.
Now go on.
- So now Eve Arden’s in charge.
- You know, I bet they
probably missed the curfew
at the prison already.
- Yeah.
- This is Curt Gowdy.
Join me, Touch Conners,
and Eve Arden
as we hunt for Beverly Garland
on the Louisiana bayou.
Hello?
- Hootie hoo, hootie hoo!
- Hey, Vera!
- Oh, hi!
[ gunshots ]
- What, are the bullets
going to fall on her?
- Whoa! Hot!
Whoa! Stingy!
- Hey, Vera!
- I just want to know if
you have any cream rinse left!
- She caught it.
[ gunshot ]
- Oh!
Think I would have learned.
- Top of the tree, Ma!
- Why don’t they come out?
- I don’t know,
kind of weird, isn’t it?
- Branch coming.
[ snake rattling ]
- Uh-oh!
- Oh ah! Here!
[ snake rattling ]
- Hey, hey,
what are you doing?
- Wait a minute,
she tied him to a tree
he can pull out of the ground?
- Is that the tree she’s in?
- Hey, Snake Conners.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh!
- Oh, good catch, Beverly.
That was worse than the gun.
- There goes bikini season
for me.
- Hoo-ah!
- [ gunshot ]
- Oh!
- Hey, he was
just a Mannix fan.
He wanted his autograph.
- Off the 3-meter board,
Beverly Garland!
- I got her!
Come on!
- Now we got
to field dress her.
- She’s dead.
- Jim.
- Are you okay?
- Lot better than I was.
- She’s dead all right,
real dead.
- Wow, those two
look like kabuki actresses.
- That snake almost got you.
- Aah!
- If there’s one thing
I can’t stand it’s snakes.
Can’t you get rid of it?
- I didn’t care much
for this one, either.
Another second,
and I’d have been dead.
- She shot it?
- Yeah.
- Before the spear got her?
- No, afterwards.
Last thing
she did before she fell.
- Redemption, ladies and
gentlemen. Redemption.
- Funny thing,
she always wanted to kill.
Kill anything,
and the last thing she did
was save his life.
- The last thing she did was
kill a snake.
- You don’t need Andrea Dworkin
to figure that one out.
- Oh.
[ outboard motor starts ]
- Well, we’re back on track.
We lost another one
at that campsite.
- And as we re-entered
the clam flowage--
- Would you please?
So this gun was actually
in Betty Lou’s handbag?
- Would you please?
- Okay, we need volunteers
to get killed at this campsite.
- How much further
we got to go now, Josie?
- Just a couple of more miles.
- Oh, let’s go.
We're not taking any chances.
They’re probably waiting
for us.
It's going to get dark
pretty soon.
I want to see
when I get out of here.
Come on, now.
- Please, call me Touch.
- I’m not interested
in how you lost those girls.
I’m only interested
in finding them again.
- I know I haven’t been
in the film for a while.
- The slightest suspicion
and they'd just as soon
kill Lieutenant Hampton
as look at her.
- $2.00 for the first minute?
I understand.
- It doesn't matter now
whether we’re seen or not.
The important thing is
to make contact.
Sure, it's a big jungle,
but we’ve got
a big force out there.
- Yeah, apparently they brought
their evil in there.
- All right.
Dick, come in here,
will you?
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
20, 40, 50 million.
[ giggling ]
- I can hardly wait to get
to that fence
and turn these diamonds
into spending money.
- Cleaning your gun
with nail polish remover.
- How much is the cut three ways
now, huh, Josie?
- Seems to me you’d like to get
to that fence, too, Lee.
- Huh?
- Oh, I, uh...
I got one of my own.
- We grew up together.
- Well, maybe he could give me
a better price.
- Boy, she looks
like Vince Edwards.
- Well, I guess they all pay
about the same.
- You never know.
How would I get
in touch with him?
- I’d rather keep that
to myself.
- Well, that’s a fine way to act
after all we’ve done for you.
- It hasn’t been
a one-way street, you know.
- No, it’s been
more like a parkway.
- Yeah, that’s right.
- Well, I don’t think it’s
very...
- Forget it, Billie.
We should be out of here
in a couple of hours.
- The movie?
- It's sure going
to seem funny
without you ordering me
around, Josie.
- Going to seem funny
without you and Vera squabbling
all the time, too.
- Boy, women convicts are
a lot more supportive.
- Sure will.
[ distant engine ]
- Oh, my ride’s here. Bye.
- Expecting something?
- Oh, it’s just
my police backup. Doh!
- Aren’t you?
They probably got this whole
jungle surrounded.
- So it’s a jungle
or a swamp?
- I don’t know.
- Poor old Vera.
- She should have let
that snake get Bob.
- What do you mean?
- Save us the trouble.
- Aw, Josie.
Can’t you think
of no other way?
He’s cute.
- He may be cute,
but as long as he can talk,
we got a couple
extra murder raps.
- If you got one,
you got a dozen.
- Why don’t you just tie him up
and leave him?
- Why should we?
- Uh, what are you guys
talking about?
- We’re close to the edge
of the jungle.
A gunshot will bring whoever’s
looking for us a-runnin'.
- So what’s my subtext here?
- What makes you so sure
somebody’s looking for us?
- You sure don’t
like gunshots, do you?
- Not when they attract
attention and get us caught.
- You don’t like them when
they kill anybody, either.
- Touch back here. Really don't
have much of a role anymore.
Can I leave?
- I wonder if you’ve
got any guts?
- She sure don’t like to see
nobody get hurt.
- Not when it’s not necessary.
- Seems to me
that this one’s necessary.
- But the sound
will bring them.
- There won’t be any sound.
Would you like to try it?
- Mumbly peg?
- Why should I?
Not my idea.
- Might make us all feel
a little closer.
- Yeah, why should we be
the only ones
with a murder rap
on our heads?
- Hey, guys, don't kill me.
Thank you.
- I’m part
of the gang now, right?
- [ imitating Elvis ]
Thank you very much.
- Okay, you two wing nuts,
I’ll do it.
- Give me your gun.
- Why should I?
I'll kill him for you
if you want.
Give me the knife.
- It’s just a little late.
Give me your gun!
- Ooh!
Are there scenes like this in
The Gun In Betty Lou’s Handbag?
- No, there
aren't scenes like this
in The Gun
In Betty Lou's Handbag!
- Did you see it?
- No!
- Wonder if it's on video?
- Would you just watch!
- Whoa,
good tunnel vision there.
- Couldn't she see that
big beige thing coming at her?
- Hey, Roy, check out the action
over there.
[ chuckles ]
- Head butt.
- ♪ When you’re a Jet,
you're a Jet all the way ♪
- Classic Mannix disarm.
- Very nice.
- No, really, I’m a cop.
You have the right to remain
sil--Oh, ow!
- Oh, she’s got her
in a Mark Eaton.
- Man!
- [ groans ]
- Pepper never
would have stood for this.
- Uh-uh.
- Ouch.
- Come on, into the water.
- Yeah, yeah!
- There you go.
- Yeah, come on!
What kind of police force is
this, anyway?
- [ imitating Sean Connery ]
Sends one of yours to the salon,
you send one of hers
to the spa.
The Chicago way.
- [ gurgling ] I said you have
the right to remain silent.
- Bad Touch! Bad Touch!
- Touch,
you're crowding the plate.
- Oh!
- That’s a Spock move.
- Swing and a miss, 0 and 2.
- Uh! Ooh!
- She’s blonde, Jim.
- Now I suppose
you want to hit me, too?
- I think you’re making
some assumptions here.
- Would you untie me?
- Hey, don’t
Touch Conners me there.
- Before you do, I’m going
to have to take you in.
- What?
- Is he a cop?
- Touch and Go--
they're cops
- I’ll go.
- Oh, he’s kissing her
her rights.
- You have the right
to remain hot.
Anything I have will be held
against you.
[ siren ]
- Yeah, here comes
the lunch wagon.
- A police boat.
- Don’t worry.
I'll stand by you.
- What?
- Pinch Conners.
- Hmm, or Pat.
- What about Pal?
- Hell?
- No, Snake.
- You have it.
- Snick?
- Slap.
- "In the Superior Court
of Los Angeles,
"a trial was held.
In a moment,
the results of that trial."
- "Fox their corporation
"for their flaming produce
washed to me.
Meyer Lansky theend."
- Oh, for--"theend."
- "The end."
- So this magnet thing
we have.
- Oh, wow,
Tom, that sounds great.
Then what’d
you do on your date?
- Well, then I walked her back
to her place.
- Yeah, and? Ha ha ha!
- Well, I shared more of
my insights into ice fishing.
- Yeah, and?
- Well, she basically implied
that she was just dying
to see me again.
- Tom, that’s great.
- Yeah, I think
it was so obvious
the way she just sort
of barked "bye,"
then rushed into her room,
slammed the door,
threw the bolt, slipped
the lock, set the chain.
Hey, might as well call her
right now.
Joel,
would you do the honors?
- Sure.
- Yeah. Heh heh.
[ phone dialing ]
[ line ringing ]
- Yep. Kid’s probably
sitting by the phone.
- Yeah.
[ ringing ]
- Yep.
[ continues ringing ]
- Hello?
- Hi.
- Who is this?
- It’s me, Tom.
- Tom who?
- Tom Servo.
- Him!
Oh, I’m glad you called.
Um, I don’t think we should
see each other anymore.
Let’s just be friends, okay?
Bye.
[ dial tone ]
- Uh, that’s too bad, Tom.
- You okay, buddy?
- Yeah, I’m fine.
Yeah, fine, big deal.
No problem
- Listen, if it gets bad
for you,
we’re here, all right?
Okay? Listen, we got
a really nice letter here.
You love letters, don’t you?
- Yeah, I like them fine.
I don’t like them any more
or less than any other day.
What do you mean by that?
- This is
from Cindy Catterling.
Let’s put that up on still star
there, Cambot.
And she writes,
"My fiancé and I
"do not watch
very much television
"since most of it is only fit
for the likes of TV's Frank.
"But we are both devoted fans
of MST3K.
"It is the only thing
on television
"that we watch
on a regular basis.
"Enclosed you will find
a wedding invitation."
- Oh, no!
- "I will be
getting married soon."
- Oh!
- "My boyfriend
and I love the show.
"I took him to see
The Sword and the Sorcerer,
"and he still asked me
out again.
"It must be true love."
- [ moaning ]
- "Also, please tell Gypsy..."
- Gypsy?!
- "...that if she can
take a short break
"from running
the higher functions
"of the Satellite of Love..."
- [ sobbing ]
"...and can shuttle down
to Earth for a few hours,
she can be one
of my bridesmaids."
- No! [ sobs ] Fine, fine!
I hope you’ll all be
very happy together, Cindy!
Oh, man, I can’t
let Gypsy see me like this.
Is my mascara running?
- No, you’re fine.
- Okay.
I got to go listen
to one of my Dan Hill albums
and just lay down.
And if Gypsy calls,
I’m on a date
with Cindy Crawford, okay?
[ sobbing ]
- Does this mean Gypsy’s
available?
- No, what
do you think?
- Shh! I’m watching me
on the U-View.
Michelle Pfeiffer and I have
just had a fabulous date.
We flew over to Paris
on the Concorde
for a late night dinner
on the Left Bank.
I drove the plane for a while.
Oh, what’s happening?
I’m dropping Michelle off
at her place?
She’s motioning for me
to come into her place?
Yes, Frank, all right! Whoo!
You old dog, you.
[ chuckles ]
Wait a minute.
What am I doing?
I’m looking at my watch?
I’m pulling a TV Guide
out from my back pocket?
I’m looking at the listings?
I'm telling Michelle
I can't stay
'cause I have to be home
in time for Baywatch?
What the hell
are you thinking?!
Stupid idiot! Oh!
[ moaning ]
Push the button, Frank.
- Shut up!